John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: Sample Tests
  - Sub-Series A: Blank Samples
    - Downey Group Will-Temperament Test, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Drake Musical Memory test, Forms A and B, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Drake: Standard Clerical Profile, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Evans-McConnell: Minnesota T-S-E Inventory, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, and scoring key.
    - Executive Appraisal Report (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Executive Potential Audit (Box 47, Folder 20)
      Blank question form and scoring key.
    - FIRO: Fundamental Interpersonal Relations Orientation (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Ferson-Stoddard: Law Aptitude Examination, LA-1 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      Third edition, Part 2. Blank question form only.
    - First National City Bank: Selecting Clerical Personnel, 1948-1968 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      Includes Test Service Bulletins from The Psychological Corporation; test validation manual, Short Employment Tests manual, and borchures.
    - Garretson: Interest Questionnaire for High School Students, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Gilford Test (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Goodenough Intelligence Test, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 26)
      For kindergartens and primary schools. Blank question form only.
    - Gordon Personal Inventory, 1955-1958 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Gordon Personal Profile, 1953-1963 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Gorham: Proverbs Test, Form I, 1954-1956 (Box 47, Folder 29)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, and scoring key. Also includes article "A Proverbs Test for Clinical and Experimental Use" by Donald Gorham reprinted from Psychological Reports, 1956.
    - Guilford: An Inventory of Factors, S T D C R, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Guilford-Martin: Inventory of Factors, G A M I N, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Guilford-Martin: Personnel Inventory, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Guilford-Zimmerman: Temperament Survey (Box 47, Folder 33)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, and scoring key.
    - Haggerty-Olson-Wickman: Behavior Rating Schedules, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Hall: Management Transaction Audit, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Harry-Durost: Essential High School Content Battery, Form AM, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 36)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - Henmon-Nelson Tests of Mental Ability, Form A, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 37)
      High school intelligence tests, grade 7-12. Blank question form only.
    - Henmon-Nelson Tests of Mental Ability, Form B, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Henmon-Nelson Tests of Mental Ability, Form C, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 39)
      High school intelligence tests, grade 7-12. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Henmon-Nelson Tests of Mental Ability, Form A, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 40)
      Intelligence test for college students. Blank question form only.
    - Henmon-Nelson Tests of Mental Ability, Form B, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Hoke: Prognostic Tst of Stenographic Ability (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Holbrook: Management Preference Survey, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Hollan Vocational Preference Inventory, Female, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Hollan Vocational Preference Inventory, Male, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - Hoppock: Job Satisfaction Blank, no.11, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - How Well Do You Know Yourself?, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 47)
      Blank question form and blank answer sheet.
    - Hunt: Aptitude Test for Nursing, Forms 1 and 2, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 48)
      George Washington University Series. Blank question form and manual of directions. For: Form 1, Arithmetic Test for Prospective Nurses; Form 1, General Science Test for Prospective Nurses; Form 1, Interest-Preference Test for Prospective Nurses
    - Hunt: Language Aptitude Test, Form 1, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 49)
      George Washington University Series. Blank question form, study sheet, and manual of directions.
    - IBM: Keyboard Exercises for IBM Card Punching Machines, Form 29-0909-1 (Box 47, Folder 50)
      Blank question form only
    - The I. E. R. Intelligence Scale C A V D, Forms 3 and 4, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 51)
      Levels M, N, O, P, and Q. Blank question form only.
    - The Inglis Tests of English Vocabulary, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - Institute for Personality and Ability Testing: Culture Free Intelligence Test (a measure of "g"), Scale 3, Forms A and B, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 53)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, and manual of directions.
    - Institute for Personality and Ability Testing: N. P. F., 1955 (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - Inventory of Activities and Interests, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 55)
      Blank question form and scoring key. There are two sets: one for Girls and Young Women and one for Boys and Young Men.
    - Iowa Every-Pupil Tests of Basic Skills, Test B: Vocabulary, Basic Study Skills, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 56)
      For grades 6-8. Blank question form only.
    - Iowa Every-Pupil Tests of Basic Skills, Test B: Work-Study Skills, Form N, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 57)
      For grades 5-9. Blank question form only.
    - Iowa Every-Pupil Tests of Basic Skills, Test C: Basic Language Skills, Form O, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 58)
    - Iowa High School Content Examination, Form M, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 59)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, Chemistry Training, Series CT1, Revised, Form A, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 60)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, English Aptitude, Series EA1, Revised, Form A, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 61)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, English Training, Series ET-2, Revised, Form M, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 62)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, French Training, Series FT1, Revised, Form A, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 63)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, Foreign Language Aptitude, Series FA-2, Revised, Form M, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 64)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, Mathematics Aptitude, Series MA-2, Revised, Form M, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 65)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, Mathematics Training, Series MT1, Revised, Form A, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 66)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, Physics Aptitude, Series PA-2, Revised, Form M, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 67)
    - Iowa Placement Examinations, Spanish Training, Series ST1, Revised, Form A, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 68)
    - Iowa Silent Reading Tests, Form AM, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 69)
      New edition. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - Jones: Health Practice Inventory, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 70)
    - Kefauver: Student Reaction to Behavior Patterns, 1934 (Box 47, Folder 71)
    - Knauber: Art Ability Test, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 72)
    - Knauber: Art Vocabulary Test, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 73)
    - Kuder Preference Record Profile, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 74)
      Report for 48 occupational fields in 6 major groups.
    - Kuhlmann-Anderson Tests, Grades I, IV, VI, IX, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 75)
    - Kuhlmann-Anderson Test G, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 76)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, and class record form.
    - Kwalwasser Test of Musical Information and Appreciation, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 77)
    - Kwalwasser-Dykema Music Tests, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 78)
      Blank answer sheet, manual of directions, and right-answers key.
    - Kwalwasser-Ruch: Test of Musical Accomplishment, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 79)
      For grades 4-12. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Law School Admission Test, 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 80)
      Bulletin of Information and broadside.
    - Lee Test of Algebraic Ability, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 81)
    - Lee-Thorpe: Occupational Interest Inventory, Advanced Series, Form A, 1943-1946 (Box 47, Folder 82)
    - Lee-Thorpe: Occupational Interest Inventory, Intermediate Series, Form A, 1943-1946 (Box 47, Folder 83)
    - Lewerenz: Orientation Test, Concerning Fundamental Aims of Education, Revision, 1935 (Box 47, Folder 84)
      The Progressive Test Series. For use in high school and college. Blank question form, manual of directions, and class record form.
    - Lewerenz: Test in Fundamental Abilities of Visual Art, 1927 (Box 47, Folder 85)
      For grades 3-12. Blank question form, manual of directions, and right-answers key. Part I, Test 1: Recognition of Proportion. Part I, Test 2: Originality of Line Drawing. Part II, Test 3,Observation of Light and Shade. Part II, Test 4: Knowle
    - Link: P. Q. or Personality Quotient Test, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 86)
      Revision. Manual of directions only.
    - Lowenfeld: Kaleidoblocs, Mosaic, Poleidoblocs, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 87)
    - Luria-Orleans: Modern Language Prognosis Test, Form A, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 88)
      For high schools and colleges. Blank question form only.
    - MacQuarrie: Test of Mechanical Ability, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 89)
    - Mahler and Associates: Personal History Record, 1959 (Box 47, Folder 90)
    - Management Research (Box 47, Folder 91)
    - Management Transaction Audit, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 92)
      Interpreting Your Scores on the Management Transaction Audit.
    - Manson: Occupational Interest Blank for Women, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 93)
    - Maslow: Social Personality Inventory for College Women, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 94)
    - Meier: Art Judgment [folder 1 of 2], 1940 (Box 47, Folder 95)
    - Meier: Art Judgment [folder 2 of 2], 1940 (Box 47, Folder 96)
    - Meier-Seashore: Art Judgment Test, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 97)
    - Mental Status Schedule, 1963 (Box 47, Folder 98)
      Manual of directions only.
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Elementary Battery, Form S, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 99)
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Intermediate Battery (Partial), Form S, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 100)
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Advanced Arithmetic Test, Form S, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Primary I Battery, Form R, 1946-1948 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      For grade 1. Blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, wrong-answer key, manual for interpreting, and class record form.
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Primary II Battery, Form R, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      For grade 2. Blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, wrong-answer key, and class record form.
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Elementary Battery, Form R, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      For grades 3-4. Blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and class record form.
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Intermediate Battery, Form A, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      For grades 4-6. Blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and class record form.
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Intermediate Battery, Form B, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      For grades 5-6. Blank answer sheet.
    - Metropolitan Achievement Tests, Advanced Battery, Form A, 1946-1948 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      For grade 7-9. Blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, manual for interpreting, and class record form.
    - Micchigan Vocabulary Profile Test, Form AM, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Miles: Industrial Test, Form J, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Miller: Advanced Personnel Test, Form H, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      Blank question form, completed answer sheet, manual of directions, and scoring key.
    - Miller: Survey of Mechanical Insight, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      Personnel Placement Series. Blank question form.
    - Miller: Survey of Object Visualization, Personnel Placement Series, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Minnesota Assembly Test (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Minnesota Rate of Manipulation Test, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      Examiner's manual only.
    - Minnesota Reading Examinations for College Students, Forms A and B, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Minnesota Speed Reading Test for College Students, Forms A and B, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - The Modern School Achievement Tests, Form I, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Mort: Judgment Characteristics of the Socially Complete Person, Form A, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Moss: Social Intelligence Test, Revised Form, 1931-1955 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      George Washington Univeristy Series. Blank question form and manual of directions. Includes First Edition, SP Edition, Short Edition, and Second Edition
    - Moss: Teaching Aptitude Test, Form 1, 1927 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      George Washington Univeristy Series. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Moss: Test for Ability to Sell, Form 1, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - National Intelligence Tet, Scale A, Form 1, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - National Intelligence Tet, Scale B, Form 2, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Nelson Biology Test, Form AM, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Nelson-Denny Reading Test, Forms A and B, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 25)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, and right-answers key.
    - Omwake: Mental Alertness Test, Revised Form, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Orleans Algebra Prognosis Test, Form A, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Orleans Algebra Prognosis Test, Revised Edition, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Orleans Geometry Prognosis Test, Form A, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Orleans-Solomon Latin Prognosis Test, Form A, 1926 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - O'Rourke Mechanical Aptitude Test, Form A, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 31)
      Blank question form and right-answers form.
    - Otis: Examination Designed Especially for Business Institutions, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Alpha Test, Form A, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 33)
      For grades 1-4. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and class record form.
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Alpha Test, Form AS, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 34)
      For grades 1-4. New edition, short form. Blank question form.
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Beta Test, Form A, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 35)
      For grades 4-9. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and class record form.
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Beta Test, Form AM, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 36)
      For senior high school and college. Blank question form and blank answer sheet.
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Gamma Test, Form C, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 37)
      For senior high school and college. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and class record form.
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Gamma Test, Form D, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Beta Test, Form EM, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 39)
      For grades 5-9. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and class record form.
    - Otis Quick-Scoring Mental Ability Test, Gamma Test, Form EM, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 40)
      For grades 5-9. Blank question form.
    - Otis Self-Administering Tests of Mental Ability, Form A, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 41)
    - Personality Dynamics Survey (Box 48, Folder 42)
      Blank interrview form.
    - Personnel Institute: Diagnostic Interviewer's Guide, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 43)
    - Picture Drawing Test (Box 48, Folder 44)
    - Pinter: Aspects of Personality, 1937 (Box 48, Folder 45)
    - Pinter: Non-Language Mental Test (Box 48, Folder 46)
    - Pinter: Non-Language Primary Mental Test, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 47)
      For kindergarten and grades 1-2. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Pinter-Cunnigham Primary Test, Form A, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 48)
      For kindergarten and grades 1-2. Blank question form, manual of directions, and class record form.
    - Pessey Senior Classification Test, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 49)
    - Pressey Senior Verifying Test, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 50)
      For grades 7-12. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Psychological Corporation: Beckman A-S Reaction Study, Revision for Business Use, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 51)
    - Psychological Corporation: Bennett Stenographic Aptitude Test, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 52)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, and right- answers key.
    - Psychological Corporation: Brainard Occupational Preference Inventory, Form A, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 53)
    - Psychological Corporation: Chicago Non-Verbal Examination, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 54)
    - Psychological Corporation: A Culture-Free Test, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 55)
    - Psychological Corporation: Culture-Free Test of Intelligence, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 56)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests, Combined Booklet, Form A, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 57)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and wrong-answer key.
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests Manual, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 58)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Abstract Reasoning, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 59)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Clerical Speed and Accuracy, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 60)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Language Usage, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 61)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Mechanical Reasoning, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 62)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Numerical Ability, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 63)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Spatial Relations, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 64)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests for Verbal Reasoning, Form A, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 65)
    - Psychological Corporation: Differential Aptitude Tests, Directions for Administration and Scoring, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 66)
    - Psychological Corporation: Scoring Keys (Box 48, Folder 67)
      Right-answers keys and wrong-answers keys.
    - Psychological Corporation: Report Forms, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 68)
      Individual report form.
    - Psychological Corporation: Edwards Personal Preference Schedule, 1953-1954 (Box 48, Folder 69)
    - Psychological Corporation: Employee Attitude Survey, Form A, Tests 1-10, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 70)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and wrong-answers key. Test 1: Verbal Comprehension. Test 2: Numerical Ability. Test 3: Visual Pursuit. Test 4: Visual Speed and Accuracy. Test 5: Space Visualizati
    - Psychological Corporation: Engineering and Physical Science Aptitude Test, 1943 (Box 48, Folder 71)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and wrong-answers key.
    - Psychological Corporation: General Clerical Test, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 72)
    - Psychological Corporation: General Clerical Test, Revised, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 73)
    - Psychological Corporation: Graves Design Judgment Test, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 74)
    - Psychological Corporation: Hopock Check-List for Self-Guidance in Choosing an Occupation, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 75)
      Blank questonf form and occupation list.
    - Psychological Corporation: How Supervise?, Forms A, B, and M, 1943-1948 (Box 48, Folder 76)
    - Psychological Corporation: Kellogg and Morton Revised Beta Examination, 1935 (Box 48, Folder 77)
      Blank question form, and scoring key.
    - Psychological Corporation: Kellogg and Morton Revised Beta Examination, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 78)
    - Psychological Corporation: Maze Test, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 79)
    - Psychological Corporation: Mechanical Comprehension, Form AA, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 80)
    - Psychological Corporation: Mechanical Comprehension, Form BB, 1941-1951 (Box 48, Folder 81)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, and wrong-answers key.
    - Psychological Corporation: Mechanical Comprehension, Form CC, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 82)
    - Psychological Corporation: Mechanical Comprehension, Form W1, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Blank answer form and class record form.
    - Psychological Corporation: Michigan Speed Reading Test, Forms I and II, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Psychological Corporation: Miller Analogies Test, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Psychological Corporation: Minnesota Clerical Test, 1933-1959 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Psychological Corporation: Minnesota Counseling Inventory, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Psychological Corporation: Minnesota Engineering Analogies Test, Form E, 1954-1955 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Psychological Corporation: Minnesota Inventory of Social Attitudes, Forms B and P, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Psychological Corporation: Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory (MMPI), 1943 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Psychological Corporation: Minnesota Paper Form Board, Series AA and BB, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      Revised. Blank question form, manual of directions, and scoring key.
    - Psychological Corporation: Modified Alpha Examination, Form 9, 1941-1951 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Psychological Corporation: Mooney Problem Check-List, Forms J and H, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Blank question form and manual of directions. Form J: Junior High School. Form H: High School.
    - Psychological Corporation: Mooney Problem Check-List, Form C, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      Blank question form and manual of directions. Form C: College.
    - Psychological Corporation: The N. I. I. P. Clerical Test (Box 49, Folder 13)
      American version. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Psychological Corporation: P-S Experience Blank, 1938 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Psychological Corporation: Raven Coloured Progressive Matrices, Sets A, Ab, and B, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Psychological Corporation: Raven Standard Progressive Matrices, Sets A, B, C, D, and E, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Psychological Corporation: Revised Alpha Examination, Form 7, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Psychological Corporation: Scovill Classification Test, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Psychological Corporation: Small Parts Dexterity Test (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Psychological Corporation: Stenographic Aptitude Test, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Psychological Corporation: Terman Concept Mastery Test, Form T, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Psychological Corporation: Test VI, Form B, 1929 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Psychological Corporation: Thurstone Edge-Marking Method of Data Analysis, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Psychological Corporation: Thurstone Interest Schedule, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Psychological Corporation: Vocational Aptitude Examination, Type E-A, 1935-1946 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Psychological Corporation: Wechsler-Bellevue Intelligence Scale, Form I, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Psychological Corporation: Wesman Personnel Classification Test, Form A, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Psychological Corporation: Wesman Personnel Classification Test, Form B, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Psychological Corporation: Wesman Personnel Tests for Industry, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      Blank question form, and scoring key. Numerical Test A. Numerical Test B. Verbal Test A. Verbal Test B.
    - Psychological Corporation: Wide Range Vocabulary Tests, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Purdue Placement Test in English, Forms A and B, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      For high schools and colleges. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Q-T Diagnostic Inventory (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Rhode Island Institute for Counseling and Personnel Service: Finger Dexterity and Wiggle Blocks (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry, and Company: Confidential Performance Report, Form C, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Richardson, Bellows, Henry, and Company: Clerical Aptitutde Test, Form A, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 35)